[
  {
    "question": "What does O(n) mean?",
    "answer": "Linear",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The type of list sorting which occurs by dividing the list in halves and merging them back together in order.",
    "answer": "Merge Sort",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the big O of a nested 'for' loop?",
    "answer": "Polynomial",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A Binary Search Tree with leaf children (its bottom-most nodes) that are no more than one node apart in their distance from the root is called what? ",
    "answer": "Balanced",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Arrays are _________ in memory. This is an incredible benefit for their usage, because it allows lookup time for any element in the array to remain O(1), constant time.",
    "answer": "Contiguous",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A _________ is a data structure the nature of which can be illustrated by imagining several plates on top of eachother.",
    "answer": "Stack",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: The difference between Big O Polynomial Classification and Big O Exponential Classification is that Polynomial increases to the power of the number of nested loops, whereas exponential increases in increments of 2 powers with each nested Loop.",
    "answer": "False",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A Hashmap uses a ________ to determine the index of an array at which an item must be stored. This is also used for extracting data out of the Hashmap",
    "answer": "Function",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The key player of a QuickSort is a(n) ______, by which the sorting algorithm flips all of the other members of the array to different sides of the list depending on whether they are less or greater.",
    "answer": "Pivot",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ can only insert data on one end and remove data on the other.",
    "answer": "Queue",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ node is a node in a Binary Tree that has no children",
    "answer": "Leaf",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The top most node of a Binary Tree is called the ______",
    "answer": "Root",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Items in a queue can only be removed from the ______",
    "answer": "Front",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false: Items in a stack can be removed by their index",
    "answer": "False",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "______ is a sort which compares each adjacent element and swaps them in the right order",
    "answer": "Bubble Sort",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "______ is when a function is calls itself within the function code",
    "answer": "Recursion",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ linked list contains pointers in each node that point to the previous and next elements",
    "answer": "Doubly",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ first search traverses each child node before moving to the next level of nodes",
    "answer": "Breadth",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ first search traverses the left subtrees first then the right subtrees",
    "answer": "Depth",
    "score": 0
  }
]